Writing is just content for AI to
steal.
Yeah, I don't think it is.
I think, as I said, I mentioned that I
mentioned as a subconscious thing, I
think
writing is, it is not just for you
because it's important that other
people read
it. I have had like people now say
nice things about my book.
I had a friend of mine just recently
say that he bought a stack of them and
gave
them to his whole team and said like,
you know, this is really useful.
He also said that the book makes you
feel that you're not alone when you're
doing
project management, that other people
have had the same experiences.
I think there are lots of reasons.
I just saw today that somebody I know
from university, who I haven't spoken
to
since, liked a video of me opening the
box with my books in it.
And the smile on my face when I'm
opening the box with books in it, I
haven't
felt that good in a long time.
So I don't think it is just training
AI.